<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ez-q Blog</title>
        <link>https://your-docusaurus-test-site.com/ez-q/blog</link>
        <description>ez-q Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alpha Release - Welcome to ez-q]]></title>
            <link>https://your-docusaurus-test-site.com/ez-q/blog/first-alpha</link>
            <guid>first-alpha</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to ez-q. This post exists as a quick introduction to ez-q as it is now in alpha (and also as some post has to be first).]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to ez-q. This post exists as a quick introduction to ez-q as it is now in alpha (and also as some post has to be first). </p><p>Ez-q aims to be a performant, scalable and, above all, simple http message queue. At time of writing we are currently at version <code>0.0.1-alpha.3</code> (catchy I know) which is a generally "working" proof of concept to illustrate the idea behind ez-q. Specifically it shows the sort of http interface and by extension intended use we are aiming for. To play with the current version please go over to <a href="/ez-q/docs/quickstart">getting started</a>.</p><p>Evidently ez-q is in it's infancy and work will be undertaken to move to a stable 1.0.0 release. To keep this on track, there are two explicit goals that should be achieved to release <code>1.0.0</code> and these will be prioritised:</p><ul><li>Make ez-q actions transactional</li><li>Create usable documentation</li></ul><p>These goals were chosen as they will allow consumers to use e-q with confidence. Moreover, these are vague at the moment and as such will be fleshed out in other forums, likely Github as to keep discussions close to the code. </p><p>Finally if you wish to poke around the code please visit the <a href="https://github.com/ez-asy/ez-q" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ez-q source code</a> as well as the <a href="https://github.com/ez-asy/ez-q-docs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ez-q-docs</a>, contributions will be welcome in both and, at time of writing, creating some sort of contribution guide is a priority - this will be advertised when complete. Nevertheless, please feel free to get involved and communicate, ideally via Github issues before a more formal system is implemented.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>release</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>